calendars.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Calendars.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
LAST UPDATED: October 2019

We at Calendars.com L.L.C. (“Calendars.com,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your,” or “yourself”) care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting, or using, websites owned and operated by Calendars.com, microsites, any other linked pages, features, content, mobile websites, and any other services we offer from time to time in connection with any of the foregoing (collectively, the “Site”), you agree to the practices and policies set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby acknowledge and consent to our collection, use, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

 This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage, even if you have accessed the websites or services of those companies through our Site or sites owned and operated by us.   
Your access to and use of the Site means you agree to the terms in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy periodically so that you understand our current privacy practices.   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service department:

  * By mail at: Calendars.com ATTN: Privacy Office 6411 Burleson Rd. Austin, TX 78744 
  * By Phone at: 1.800.366.3645

 **WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT** **  
**We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us, transaction information, technology-enabled services, and information we collect about you from third party sources. The following are examples of information we may collect and share: ****

  * Contact Information. We may collect your name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number.
  * Payment Information. We may collect your credit card number and billing address. 
  * Information you post. We may collect information you post in a public space on our site. This may include our Ratings & Review feature. 
  * Social Media Information. We may collect information you post on our social media pages. We may also collect your social media profile information.
  * Information You Submit. For example, we may collect information when you contact us through the "Live Chat" feature on our site.
  * Demographic Information. For example, we may collect your age, gender and zip code.
  * Device Information. For example, we may collect the type of device you use to access our Platforms. It may also include your device identification number, IP address or mobile operating system.
  * Location Information. For example, we may collect precise location information from your device. For more information about your choices related to location information, see the Choices section below.
  * Other Information. If you use our website, we may collect information about the browser you are using. We may look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. 

**HOW WE COLLECT & USE INFORMATION  
**We are committed to protecting your privacy. Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your e-mail address with any other company for marketing purposes without your consent. 

Calendars.com collects information in different ways:

  *  **Directly from you**. When you 
    * Make a purchase on our platform
    * Make a return or exchange
    * Create a Calendars.com account
    * Track an order online
    * Sign up to receive promotional emails or text messages
    * Participate in one of our promotional sweepstakes, contests, or surveys, 
    * Use the Ratings & Reviews service
    * Submit a request to our Customer Service team
    * Interact with Calendars.com’s social media pages  

  *  **Passively**. When you
    * Visit or navigate to the Calendars.com platform
    * Click on sponsored links or third-party advertisements  

  *  **From Third Parties**. We may receive information about you from other sources. For example, this may include
    * Our business partners, including online advertising networks and companies that co-sponsor our promotions
    * Social media platforms including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest and Youtube
    * Companies that provide information to supplement what we already know about you  

  *  **By combining information**. We may
    * Combine information we collect about you from the different devices you use to access our platforms
    * Combine information we get from third parties with information we already have about you

We may use the information we collect for the following reasons:

  *  **To Provide Our Products and Services.**  This could include fulfilling your requests for products or services. It could also include processing purchases or return transactions.
  *  **To Improve Our Products and Services.**  We may use your information to make our Platforms and stores better. We may also use your information to customize your experience with us.
  *  **To Understand Your Interests.**  For example, we may use your information to better understand what products interest you.
  *  **To Respond to Your Requests or Questions.**  This may include responding to your customer feedback.
  *  **To Communicate With You.**  We may communicate with you about your account or our relationship. We may also contact you about this Privacy Policy or our Platform Terms & Conditions
  *  **For Marketing Purposes.**  We may provide you with information about new products and special offers. We may use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. We may tell you about new features or updates. These might be third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. For more information about your choices related to these communications, see the [Choices](https://www.kohls.com/feature/privacy-policy.jsp#choicesregardingyourinfo) section below.
  *  **For Security Purposes.**  This could include protecting our company and our customers. It may also include protecting our Platforms.
  *  **As Otherwise Permitted By Law or As We May Notify You.**

 **HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION  
** We may share your information in the following ways:

  *  **Internally**. We may share your information within the Calendars.com family of companies. This includes our affiliates and subsidiaries.
  *  **On our Platforms**. For example, we may display information you post on our Ratings & Reviews feature. 
  * **With Our Service Providers.** We may share your information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, this may include merchandise vendors and payment processors. It may also include companies that send emails on our behalf.
  *  **With Our Business Partners**. For example, this may include third parties that provide services related to our business. It may also include a third party that co-sponsors a contest or promotion.
  *  **With Third Parties for Marketing Purposes**. This may include third parties in whose products or services we believe you may be interested. These third parties may also share your information with others. These third parties may use your information for their own marketing purposes or the marketing purposes of others. This may include the delivery of interest-based advertising.
  *  **With Any Successors to All or Part of Our Business**. For example, if Calendars.com merges with, acquires or is acquired by another business entity. This may include an asset sale, corporate reorganization or other change of control.
  *  **To Comply With the Law or To Protect Ourselves**. For example, this could include responding to a court order or subpoena. It could also include sharing information if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We may share information when we are investigating a potential fraud. This could include fraud we think has occurred during a sweepstakes or promotion. We may also share information if you are the winner of a sweepstakes or other contest with anyone who requests a winner's list.
  *  **For Other Reasons We May Describe to You.**

 **CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION  
** The following describes various types of technologies we will use when you interact with the Site and your choices regarding those technologies:

Cookies, Pixel Tags, and Flash Cookies  
On the Site, and other digital platforms, we use Cookies, Pixel Tags, and Flash Cookies. A Cookie is a small piece of code sent by a website that is store on your hard disk by your computer’s browser. A pixel tag (also known as a tracking pixel, web beacon, or clear GIF) is an embedded image on a website that monitors a website activity. A Flash Cookie is a data file stored on your computer by the websites that you visit. Flash Cookies provide similar functionality as Cookies, but are based on different technology, provide richer data collections, and are persistent.

At Calendars.com, we use two kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only for as long as your browser remains open. We use session cookies, for example, to add items to your shopping bag. Persistent cookies last from visit to visit; they do not go away when you exit your browser. At Calendars.com, we use persistent cookies to give you a more personalized shopping experience and to help you navigate our Site more efficiently. For example, we use persistent cookies to show you items you have previously browsed.

Managing cookies preferences differs from browser to browser so please refer to your browser for further information. If you would like to disable cookies and web beacons from Calendars.com, please use the help function in your web browser to restrict cookies from our Site. If you block cookies from Calendars.com, you may not be able to make purchases on our Site. Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Calendars.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Website Optimization Services  
Calendars.com shares data with Google Analytics and Monetate to understand and optimize website performance and enhance site usability for our customers. These tools run in the background of our site analyzing site usage information and then returning reports to us through an encrypted connection. Each is required to maintain data securely and confidentially and is not permitted to share data collected with anyone other than Calendars.com. Credit card or password information is not collected by or shared with either Google Analytics or Monetate. 

Interest-Based or Online Behavioral Advertising  
Calendars.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve interest-based advertisements. These companies compile information from various online sources (including mobile-enabled browsers and applications) to match user profiles with ads we believe will be most relevant, interesting and timely based on that user profile.

Display Advertising  
We may utilize Google Analytics tools, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Double-Click Campaign Manager Integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Impression Recording to support display advertising. We may frame or mask another website so that the look, feel and interface simulate the experience of browsing a genuine Calendars.com web page. Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third part sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.

Social Network Programs  
Calendars.com has relationships with several social networks. These companies allow Calendars.com to match users that have shown interest in Calendars.com with their social profiles in order to deliver relevant, interest-based ads on those companies’ networks. 

Do Not Track  
Calendars.com does not currently have the capability to recognize browser Do Not Track signals. Please use the following link to learn more about DNT: <http://www.allaboutdnt.org/>

Interactions with Third-Party Websites and Content  
We may enable you to navigate to third-party sites and services, or otherwise display third-party content. We do this for your convenience. We do not endorse or generally have any affiliation with these third parties. We do not control and are not responsible for their web practices. Whether the third-party content appears within our web environment (like a map frame), or you leave our web site for another site to view it, those service provider's terms, conditions, and privacy policies govern your online experience. Please view their terms of service and privacy policies if you have any question about their practices.

Here's a partial list of the sites or content of these third parties: 

  1. Interactive Maps  
We may facilitate easy access to the online maps of content providers like Google, Microsoft, and Yahoo! There you can get quick location, driving, and contact information for our stores.

  2. Sweepstakes, Contests, and Survey Sites  
We may rely on the expertise of third-party service providers to run sweepstakes, contests, and surveys. Navigation to these sites may be seamless so that it appears you're still in our Site environment. In these cases, the third-party's privacy policy may apply to any personal information you provide in connection with the event. So please take note of who's running the event in question; and the terms, conditions, and policies that apply.

  3. Social Networking or Other User-Generated-Content Sites, and Other Websites  
We may at times facilitate easy access to third-party sites, like social networking sites and other sites that host user-generated content. This may include easy click-through access or even "single sign-on" to these sites. The third-party's privacy policy applies to any personal information you provide at these sites.

 **CUSTOMER PREFERENCES AND OPT-OUT CHOICES**

E-mail 

  * Unsubscribe by signing into your account on Calendars.com, clicking on my account and indicating your opt-in preference.
  * Use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any promotional email sent by Calendars.com
  * Write us by mail at: Calendars.com ATTN: Privacy Office 6411 Burleson Rd. Austin, TX 78744  

Mobile Messaging

  * If you’ve signed up for mobile text messaging offers but later decide you no longer wish to receive offers from us, simply follow the opt-out instructions included in the mobile message.  

Direct Mail or Telemarketing

  * Write us by mail at: Calendars.com ATTN: Privacy Office 6411 Burleson Rd. Austin, TX 78744 
  * By Phone at: 1.800.366.3645  

Online Behavioral Advertising

  * Please use the following link for the NAI website:
    * <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>  

  * Please use the following link for the DAA website:
    * <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>

Third Party Sharing

  * Write us by mail at: Calendars.com ATTN: Privacy Office 6411 Burleson Rd. Austin, TX 78744 
  * By Phone at: 1.800.366.3645

Do Not Track

  * Calendars.com does not currently have the capability to recognize browser Do Not Track signals.
    * Please use the following link to learn more about DNT.
      * <http://www.allaboutdnt.org/>

 **OWNERSHIP OF CUSTOMER DATA  
If Calendars.com or any of its subsidiaries is sold to or otherwise acquired by a third party, all Calendars.com data assets will become the property of the acquiring party. Such a party will be subject to any consent(s), opt-outs or other customer conditions on data.  A change in data ownership may or may not include a notice on the primary online sites of Calendars.com, Inc. or the affected subsidiary sites.**

 **DISCLOSURES**  
Information About Children Under 13  
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act imposes requirements on Web sites that collect personal information about children under 13 (for example - name, address, e-mail address, social security number, etc.) The Site is intended for use by individuals 13 years of age or older. Our policy is not to collect any Personal Information on any person under 13. For this reason, our online sweepstakes, e-mail and mobile sign-ups are restricted to entrants who are at least 13. Do not submit any Personal Information of any person under 13 years of age.

If this policy changes, Calendars.com will revise this portion of its notice of privacy practices and will comply with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, which includes providing notice and choice to each child's parent or guardian before collecting any personal information.

 **Your California Privacy Rights**  
Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us once per calendar year for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of personal information shared with third parties and used for direct marketing purposes and the name and address of the third parties that received such personal information. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Calendars.com, L.L.C., 6411 Burleson Road, Austin, TX 78744. In your request, please specify that you want a "Your Calendars.com's California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response.

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. If you’re concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about Calendars.com.
